{
    "id": "7ac68f3d4c1e4616a87b7fd9012aa232",
    "title": "Idiomatic Expressions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is oily ..................... but she does not have a kind heart.",
            "description": "Oily tongued means excessively smooth-spoken",
            "answers": [
                "skinned",
                "tongued"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b442afae60a94b8ea37cc84c7f095de3"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Can I borrow some milk?’ ‘Why not? We have ...................... and some to spare.’",
            "description": "To have more than enough.",
            "answers": [
                "a lot",
                "enough",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "018f310f297640d0ad910670c9419f16"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t depend on him. He is a man of ..............................",
            "description": "Used to refer to a person who has a weak character",
            "answers": [
                "feather",
                "straw",
                "red"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "09fb05be618044e18e62afb55fcc2ec2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We were already going through a financial crisis so dad's illness was a bolt from the ……………………….",
            "description": "A sudden and unexpected event that is usually harmful.",
            "answers": [
                "sky",
                "hell",
                "blue"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "42c8d4988c2743229d7893157b634320"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her refusal to answer his phone calls was a red rag to the .........................",
            "description": "An act or utterance that is going to provoke someone.",
            "answers": [
                "tiger",
                "elephant",
                "bull"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0220bca0f6dd4b989fc5bc89630b24bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "After wasting two hours searching for the cat, we realized we were on a wild ........................... chase.",
            "description": "A wild goose chase is a search that is completely unsuccessful.",
            "answers": [
                "cat",
                "goose",
                "crow"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e22a29f372dd4936801a9ddc2abc87be"
        },
        {
            "question": "When the business failed, years of hard work went up in ...........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "vain",
                "smoke",
                "smog"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cf65f3c997834d1f8b1a8466a0336c6c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is every ......................... a gentleman.",
            "description": "Every inch means thoroughly.",
            "answers": [
                "ounce",
                "pound",
                "inch"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "058c2f26ab8e4beca6ed71a9ff083d58"
        },
        {
            "question": "He thinks he is highly influential but he is actually a big ....................... in a small pond.",
            "description": "When you are a big fish in a small pond, you have a lot of influence only over a small area.",
            "answers": [
                "turtle",
                "frog",
                "fish"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c671c2badd824ca6bc0c59eb4ea1bce6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Giving advice to this worthless fellow is like casting pearls before a .........................",
            "description": "To cast pearls before a swine is to talk wisely to fools.",
            "answers": [
                "dog",
                "monkey",
                "swine"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9a6d187e38564e62ab19191ba7f3ae62"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a tough guy and will weather any ……………………….",
            "description": "To weather a storm is to face difficulties. ",
            "answers": [
                "tornado",
                "hurricane",
                "storm"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ce5b84619ee245f6afdea8d2d8385c68"
        },
        {
            "question": "",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6bfc391c6e544e3aa82987c7fb594c6"
        }
    ]
}